aipac.org 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | AIPAC.org

## AIPAC PRIVACY POLICY

Effective Date: 4/11/2016

This privacy policy applies to [www.aipac.org](http://www.aipac.org/) and [https://aipac.secure.force.com](https://aipac.secure.force.com/) owned and operated by AIPAC. This privacy policy describes how AIPAC collects and uses the personal information you provide on our websites: [www.aipac.org](http://www.aipac.org/) and [https://aipac.secure.force.com](https://aipac.secure.force.com/). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Statement, you should contact membership@aipac.org. 

AIPAC firmly believes in protecting the privacy of our members as well as visitors to our website.  

Financial information (such as credit card numbers, expiration dates, etc.) and personal information (such as name, email address, zip code, etc.) that you provide on our website or via mail is handled with utmost security and privacy. This information is used solely for our own business purposes, such as to process a donation or to contact you at a later date, and is not shared or sold to outside organizations or companies. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy.

Names and mail addresses are occasionally shared as part of list exchanges with like-minded organizations. AIPAC has and will continue to honor all requests from individuals that their names and addresses not be exchanged or shared to any other entity. To request that your email address not be shared as part of these list exchanges, please email [membership@aipac.org](mailto:membership@aipac.org).

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information:  

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if AIPAC is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

### Security

AIPAC takes the utmost care to protect the safety and security of your online transactions by using industry-standard encryption and security protocols. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). The credit card information provided is only entered through the site but is stored on our third party payment gateway.

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at [membership@aipac.org](mailto:membership@aipac.org).

**User Access and Choice**

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend or delete/remove, ask to have it removed from a public forum, directory or testimonial on our site or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing us at [membership@aipac.org](mailto:membership@aipac.org) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information for seven years to comply with our accounting and legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, or you can contact us at [membership@aipac.org](mailto:membership@aipac.org).

**How We Use Cookies and Tracking Technologies**

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by AIPAC and our partners [digital marketing providers], affiliates, or analytics or service providers [advocacy engagement providers]. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing these types of tracking technologies.

We use Local Shared Objects, such as Flash cookies and Local Storage, such as HTML 5, to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity also use Flash cookies or HTML 5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML 5. To manage Flash cookies, please click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). 

We use cookies to manage our users' email subscriptions, web analytics, content optimization, and for website security. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

**How We Use Analytics / Log Files**

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality.  

**Behavioral Advertising/Re-Targeting**

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may [opt-out](mailto:membership@aipac.org). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

**Testimonials**

We may display personal testimonials on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [membership@aipac.org](mailto:membership@aipac.org).

**Links to 3rd Party Sites**

Our Site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of AIPAC. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

**Social Media Features**

Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Changes to this Policy**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Us**

If you have questions about this policy, please contact us at:

AIPAC  
251 H Street NW  
Washington, DC 20001
